{
    "subject": "resource/Newhaven_Harbour_railway_station",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Lewes",
    "human_readable": "Newhaven Harbour railway station is about Lewes.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9698691964149475,
            "question": "Could Newhaven Harbour railway station be used to travel to Lewes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9645439386367798,
            "question": "If someone wanted to visit Lewes, would they likely use Newhaven Harbour railway station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.959889829158783,
            "question": "Where is Lewes located relative to Newhaven Harbour railway station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9502087235450745,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the relationship between Newhaven Harbour railway station and Lewes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9047546982765198,
            "question": "Is Lewes near a railway station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8777162432670593,
            "question": "What is Newhaven Harbour railway station about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6609046459197998,
            "question": "What other places might be near Newhaven Harbour railway station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6076043248176575,
            "question": "What kind of town is Lewes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4689391255378723,
            "question": "Are there any important landmarks or features in Lewes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4287255108356476,
            "question": "What are some popular activities or attractions in Lewes?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Newhaven Harbour railway station is about Lewes.",
            "html": "dbpedia_526_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any important landmarks or features in Lewes?",
            "html": "dbpedia_526_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of town is Lewes?",
            "html": "dbpedia_526_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other places might be near Newhaven Harbour railway station?",
            "html": "dbpedia_526_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_526_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_526_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_526_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_526_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_526_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_526_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_526_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_526_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_526_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_526_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n**Explanation:**\n\nThe documents describe train travel between Newhaven Harbour and Lewes, indicating a geographical relationship between the two locations.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\nThe documents provide information on train travel between Newhaven Harbour and Lewes, including details such as travel time (11m), number of trains per day (37/36), first and last train departures, etc. This indicates that the railway station at Newhaven Harbour is indeed related to Lewes in terms of train travel, making the triple correct according to the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information on train journeys between Newhaven Harbour and Lewes, which implicitly supports the statement that Newhaven Harbour railway station is near Lewes. The travel times and schedules for trains between these two locations are detailed, indicating their proximity to each other."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}